Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
- Box: 39, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Final Report, 1967; Publication (Box 39, Folder 21)
    Author: Permanent Technical Committee on Labor Matters
    Notes: 12-14 June 1967
- Box: 39, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions and International Activities, Publication (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Box: 39, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The ILO Today, 1967; Publication (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Nobel Peace Prize, 1969; Publication (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: Britain and the I.L.O., 1969; Publication (Box 39, Folder 23)
    Author: C. Wilfred Jenks
    Notes: February 4, 1969
  - Item 4: Le Canada et la Fondation de L'Organisation Internationale du Travail, Publication (Box 39, Folder 23)
    Author: Frank E. Burke, John A. Munro
    Language: French; English.
  - Item 5: U.S. Participation in the International Labor Organization Not Effectively Managed, 1970; Publication (Box 39, Folder 23)
    Notes: December 22, 1970
  - Item 6: Havana Charter for an International Trade Organization, 1948; Publication (Box 39, Folder 23)
    Notes: March 24, 1948
- Box: 39, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: How to be Interviewed, Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Training Guide on the Techniques of Qualitative Interviews, 1948; Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Employee Selection: The Supervisors Role, Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
    Author: Donald R. Berry, Walter A. Pachuk
  - Item 4: The Employment Interview Techniques of Questioning, Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
    Author: Richard H. Magee
  - Item 5: Interviewing and Counselling, 1964; Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: Merchandising Your Job Talents, Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: Interviewing in Social Security, 1961; Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
    Author: Elizabeth de Schweinitz & Karl de Schweinitz
  - Item 8: Interviewing Techniques for the Non Personnel Executive, Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
    Author: Personnel Testing Service
  - Item 9: Interviewing Techniques for the Non Personnel Executive, Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: How to Conduct Better Performance Appraisal Interviews, Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
    Author: Robert L. Noland, Joseph J. Moyland
  - Item 11: How to Conduct Better Performance Appraisal Interviews, Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Item 12: Interviewing Theories and Techniques, 1963; Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
    Author: U.S. Navy Department
  - Item 13: Effective Employment Interviewing, Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
    Author: Administrative Management Society
  - Item 14: The Role of Inventory Changes During Expansion and Contraction, 1962; Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Item 15: Inventory Fluctuations, Price Level Changes, and Economic Growth, 1962; Publication (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Box: 39, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Your Share in America's Prosperity, Publication (Box 39, Folder 25)
    Author: J. Whitney Bunting
- Box: 39, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Impact of U.S. Foreign Direct Investment on U.S. Employment and Trade, Publication (Box 39, Folder 26)
    Author: National Foreign Trade Council
- Box: 39, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Private Investment in Latin America, 1964; Publication (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Box: 39, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Investment Laws and Regulations in Africa, 1965; Publication (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Box: 39, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Foreign Business Investments in the United States, Publication (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Box: 39, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Foreign Private Investments in the Latin American Free-Trade Area, 1961; Publication (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Entrepreneurship and Industrialization in Latin America, 1966; Publication (Box 39, Folder 30)
    Author: Lawrence G. Franko, Michael Dixon, Carlos Arturo Marulanda
- Box: 39, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: A Study in Investment Behavior by Industry, 1964; Publication (Box 39, Folder 31)
    Author: Fumimasa Hamada
- Box: 39, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Work for All, 1967; Publication (Box 39, Folder 32)
    Author: Department of Finance
  - Item 2: Report of the Great Britain Joint Working Party on the Economy of Northern Ireland, 1962; Publication (Box 39, Folder 32)
    Author: Great Britain Joint Working Party
- Box: 39, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: The Iron and Steel Industry, 1914; Publication (Box 39, Folder 33)
    Author: The Merchants' Association of New York
- Box: 39, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: The Saugus Ironworks Restoration, Publication (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Box: 39, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: The First Iron Works Restoration, Publication (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Box: 39, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Professor Irvine's Economics in Australian Labour History, 1966; Publication (Box 39, Folder 36)
    Author: Bruce McFarlane
- Box: 39, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Economic Conditions in Member and Associated Countries of the OEEC, 1961; Publication (Box 39, Folder 37)
    Author: Organisation for European Economic Co-Operation
- Box: 39, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: What Shall I Read on Japan, Publication (Box 39, Folder 38)
    Author: Hyman Kublin
  - Item 2: Materials on Japan, Publication (Box 39, Folder 38)
    Author: Japan Society
- Box: 39, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Occupied Japan's Trade with Soviet China, 1951; Publication (Box 39, Folder 39)
    Author: Richard L-G. Deverall
    Notes: February 1, 1951
- Box: 39, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Labour and Economic Development in Japan Since the War, 1962; Publication (Box 39, Folder 40)
    Author: Ichiro Nakayama
  - Item 2: The Japanese Economy, Publication (Box 39, Folder 40)
    Author: Federation of British Industries
- Box: 39, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Helping to End Economic Discrimination, Publication (Box 39, Folder 41)
    Author: J.X. Cohen
  - Item 2: Job Equality and the Jewish Worker, 1954; Publication (Box 39, Folder 41)
    Author: National Community Relations Advisory Council
    Notes: November 16, 1954
- Box: 39, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: On Combating Racism, Publication (Box 39, Folder 42)
    Author: David W. Petegorsky
- Box: 39, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Job Rating, Publication (Box 39, Folder 43)
    Author: National Metal Trades Association
  - Item 2: Job Rating, Publication (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Item 3: How to Rate Jobs and Men, Publication (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Item 4: A Study of Management Engineering Practices in Texas, 1949; Publication (Box 39, Folder 43)
    Author: Texas A&M
    Notes: February 1949
  - Item 5: Guide for Analyzing Jobs, 1944; Publication (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Item 6: A Guide to Job Analysis, 1970; Publication (Box 39, Folder 43)
    Author: T.H. Boydell
  - Item 7: Training Reference Manual for Job Analysis, 1944; Publication (Box 39, Folder 43)
    Notes: June 1944
  - Item 8: The Development, Analysis, and Experimental Application of Worker-Oriented Job Variables, 1964; Publication (Box 39, Folder 43)
    Author: Ernest J. McCormick
  - Item 9: Training & Reference Manual for Job Analysis, 1965; Publication (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Item 10: Job Analysis Bibliography, 1962; Publication (Box 39, Folder 43)
    Author: Joseph E. Morsh
- Box: 39, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: A Handbook for Job Restructuring, 1970; Publication (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Item 2: Industrial Job Analysis, 1946; Publication (Box 39, Folder 44)
    Author: J.M. Tedford
  - Item 3: The Guide Line Method of Job Evaluation, 1963; Publication (Box 39, Folder 44)
    Author: Smyth & Murphy Associates
  - Item 4: Personnel Manager's Guide to Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 39, Folder 44)
    Author: George F Thomason
  - Item 5: Industrial Job Evaluation Systems, 1947; Publication (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Item 6: The Time-Span of Discretion in Job Analysis, Publication (Box 39, Folder 44)
    Author: J.M.M. Hill
  - Item 7: The Classification System used in Job-Task Analysis, Publication (Box 39, Folder 44)
    Author: Health Services Mobility Study
  - Item 8: Job Analysis and Job Description Writing, Publication (Box 39, Folder 44)
    Author: Civil Service Commission of Canada
  - Item 9: Unclassified Ad 275 505, Publication (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Item 10: A Point Plan for Rating Jobs, 1940; Publication (Box 39, Folder 44)
    Author: N.G. Mills
    Notes: December 1940
- Box: 39, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Manual for Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 39, Folder 45)
    Author: Oklahoma Civil Service Commission
  - Item 2: Personnel Information Bulletin, 1962; Publication (Box 39, Folder 45)
- Box: 40, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation, Severance Pay, Lost Money, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Box: 40, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Occupational Information on Furniture Manufacturing in North Carolina, 1947; Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
    Author: N.C. State Employment Service Division
- Box: 40, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Techniques of Job Evaluation and Merit Rating in the Library, 1947; Publication (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Author: A. H. Munson
    Notes: February 13, 1947
- Box: 40, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Explanation of the Classification Act of 1949 by Titles and Sections, Publication (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Box: 40, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Three Studies of Job Inventory Procedures: Selecting Duty Categories, Interviewing, and Sampling, 1969; Publication (Box 40, Folder 5)
    Author: Clyde C. Mayo
    Notes: November 1969
  - Item 2: Construction and Administration of Ten Air Force Job Inventories, 1969; Publication (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: A Method for Determining Job Types for Low Aptitude Airmen, 1969; Publication (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Box: 40, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Industrial Job Evaluation Systems, 1943; Publication (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Author: War Manpower Commission
    Notes: August 1943
  - Item 2: Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Author: J. Walker Morris
  - Item 3: Joint Union-Management Job Evaluation in the Canadian Steel Industry, Publication (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Author: McMaster University
  - Item 4: Job Evaluation and Merit Rating, 1970; Publication (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Classification Case Studies, Publication (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Box: 40, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation, 1960; Publication (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Box: 40, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: A Theory of Adult Motivation, 1961; Publication (Box 40, Folder 8)
    Author: Psychological Service of Pittsburgh
- Box: 40, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Contracts of Employment Act, 1963; Publication (Box 40, Folder 9)
    Author: E.G. Rutter, K. Ottaway
  - Item 2: Do the Seniority Rights of Employees Survive an Expired Contract?, Publication (Box 40, Folder 9)
    Author: Eugene A. Hoffman
  - Item 3: Security and Change, 1961; Publication (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Do The Seniority Rights of Employees Survive an Expired Contract?, Publication (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Security of Employment, Publication (Box 40, Folder 9)
    Author: Eric Moonman
- Box: 40, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Alabama Job Guide for Young Workers, 1966; Publication (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Job Guide for Young Workers, Publication (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Job Guide for Young Workers, Publication (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Career Guide for Demand Occupations, Publication (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Technical Occupations, 1961; Publication (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Job Guide for Young Workers, Publication (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: 44 Office Job Classifications and Specifications, Publication (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Box: 40, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Standard Job Class Definitions, Publication (Box 40, Folder 11)
    Author: Public Personnel Association
- Box: 40, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Identification, Measurement and Factor Analyses of "Worker-Oriented" Job Variables, 1963; Publication (Box 40, Folder 12)
    Author: George G. Gordon
  - Item 2: Manual of Job Descriptions in the Cotton Textile Industry, Publication (Box 40, Folder 12)
    Author: Department of Labour and National Service
- Box: 40, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Electrical and Electronic Technologies, Publication (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Box: 40, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Mechanical Drafting and Design Technology, Publication (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Box: 40, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Occupations in Numerically Controlled Metal-Cutting Machining, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Box: 40, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Demobilization and Jobs, 1944; Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
    Author: Charles W. Eliot
- Box: 40, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Editor's Guide Book for College Newspapers, 1949; Publication (Box 40, Folder 17)
    Author: New York Herald Tribune
- Box: 40, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Journey to Work; Manhattan Central Business District, 1964; Publication (Box 40, Folder 18)
    Author: New York - New Jersey Transportation Agency
  - Item 2: Journey-to-Work Transportation Analysis, 1964; Publication (Box 40, Folder 18)
    Author: New York Office of Transportation
  - Item 3: Journey to Work in the Tri-State Region, 1964; Publication (Box 40, Folder 18)
    Author: Tri- State Transportation Committee
  - Item 4: Commuting in the Syracuse Labor Market Area, 1960; Publication (Box 40, Folder 18)
    Notes: January 1960
- Box: 40, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Journey to Work: Selected References 1960-67, 1968; Publication (Box 40, Folder 19)
    Author: Council of Planning Librarians
- Box: 40, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Judicial Retirement System, 1965; Publication (Box 40, Folder 20)
    Author: Kentucky Legislative Research Commission
  - Item 2: Judges' Salaries and Retirement, 1968; Publication (Box 40, Folder 20)
    Author: Committee on the District of Columbia
    Notes: May 1, 1968
  - Item 3: Judicial Salaries and Retirement Plans in the United States, 1968; Publication (Box 40, Folder 20)
    Author: The American Judicature Society
  - Item 4: Judicial Salary Survey Supplement, 1970; Publication (Box 40, Folder 20)
    Author: Rae N. Selig
- Box: 40, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Expenditure and Employment for Selected Large Governmental Units, 1969; Publication (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Box: 40, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Business Conditions in Kalamazoo, 1963; Publication (Box 40, Folder 22)
    Author: Sherrill Cleland
- Box: 40, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Moral Foundation and the Impact of Keynesianism, 1964; Publication (Box 40, Folder 23)
    Author: Wilhelm Ropke
- Box: 40, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Rol Nik Krupskot V Shoudel Stue Shhody, 1967; Publication (Box 40, Folder 24)
    Author: E.G. Osovskii
- Box: 40, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Arbeidsbestel en Participatie, 1967; Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Author: J. Ijzerman
  - Item 2: Oslobodenje Rada I Samoupravljanje, 1967; Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Author: Rajko Danilovic
  - Item 3: Istorijska Uloga Radnicke Klase, 1967; Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: The Right to Work and the Right to Strike, Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Author: H.B. Acton
  - Item 5: Workers: A Special Section, 1972; Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Author: Liberation
  - Item 6: Labour on the March, 1967; Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Author: Cyprus Ministry of Labour and Social Insurance
    Notes: October, 1967
  - Item 7: Population Salariee et Loisirs, Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Author: Federation Suisse Pour L'Education des Adultes
  - Item 8: The African Worker in South Africa, 1971; Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Author: Robert Birley
  - Item 9: New England Labor and the Economy at the Year-End, 1963; Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Notes: December 29, 1963
  - Item 10: Arbete I Utlandet, 1966; Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Author: Svenska Industritjanstemannaforbundet
  - Item 11: Aboriginal Labour, 1971; Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Author: F. Stevens
    Notes: March 1971
  - Item 12: So Leben Sie Druben-So Leben Wir Hier, Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Author: Von Albert Muller
  - Item 13: La Reglementation Relative a L'Emploi des Travailleurs Etrangers, 1968; Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Author: Federation des Industries Belges
- Box: 40, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Le Mouvement Syndical Ouest Africain D'Expression Francaise, 1965; Publication (Box 40, Folder 26)
    Author: Centre de Documentation Economique et Sociale Africaine
- Box: 40, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Labor Party: A Speech, 1869; Publication (Box 40, Folder 27)
    Author: E.H. Heywood
- Box: 40, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Performance of Arkansas Workers, 1963; Publication (Box 40, Folder 28)
    Author: Ethel B. Jones
- Box: 40, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Report of the United States Government Delegates to a Meeting of the International Labor Organization, 1971; Publication (Box 40, Folder 29)
    Notes: December 4-14, 1971
- Box: 40, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: First Steps, 1966; Publication (Box 40, Folder 30)
    Author: W.J.H. Harris
  - Item 2: Labour and the Gold Fields, 1968; Publication (Box 40, Folder 30)
    Author: Australian Society for the Study of Labour History
- Box: 40, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Osterreichs Arbeiter fur die Unabhangigkeit, Publication (Box 40, Folder 31)
    Author: Theodor Heinishc
- Box: 40, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Courrier Hebdomadaire, 1961; Publication (Box 40, Folder 32)
    Notes: July 22, 1961
- Box: 40, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Bibliographical Material on Foreign Labor Problems, 1949; Publication (Box 40, Folder 33)
    Author: M. Gardner Clark & Bradford Shaw
    Notes: September 12-14, 1949
  - Item 2: A Select Bibliography on Labour Problems, 1958; Publication (Box 40, Folder 33)
    Author: India Ministry of Labour & Employment
  - Item 3: Selected References for Labor Attaches, 1959; Publication (Box 40, Folder 33)
    Notes: July 1959
  - Item 4: Labour in Society, 1969; Publication (Box 40, Folder 33)
    Author: Toronto Public Libraries
- Box: 40, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Arbetsmarknads Terminologi, Publication (Box 40, Folder 34)
    Author: Svenska Arbetsgivareforeningens Bibliotek
- Box: 40, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: A Yankee Toolmaker Abroad, Publication (Box 40, Folder 35)
    Author: American Committee
  - Item 2: Labour in Britain and the Six, 1962; Publication (Box 40, Folder 35)
    Author: Val Schur
- Box: 40, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: L'Aide Aux Travailleurs Migrants, 1968; Publication (Box 40, Folder 36)
    Author: Hommes et Migrations
- Box: 40, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Labor Problems in West Germany, 1952; Publication (Box 40, Folder 37)
    Author: U.S. Office of the U.S. High Commissioner for Germany
- Box: 40, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: A Bibliography on Labor in Ghana, 1962; Publication (Box 40, Folder 38)
    Notes: February 1962
- Box: 40, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: A Bibliography on Labor in Ghana, 1962; Publication (Box 40, Folder 39)
- Box: 40, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Labour in the Sixties, Publication (Box 40, Folder 40)
- Box: 40, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: The Progress of the Working Classes in the Last Half Century, 1885; Publication (Box 40, Folder 41)
    Author: Robert Giffen
  - Item 2: Prometheans or Troglodytes? The English Working Class and the Dialectics of Incorporation, 1967; Publication (Box 40, Folder 41)
    Author: Nigel Young
    Notes: Summer 1967
  - Item 3: 21 Years of the Labour L.C.C., Publication (Box 40, Folder 41)
    Author: London Labour Party
  - Item 4: The British Worker in Retreat, Publication (Box 40, Folder 41)
    Author: C.H. Norman
  - Item 5: The Worker in Industry, Publication (Box 40, Folder 41)
    Author: Conservative Political Centre
  - Item 6: British Workers in the War, Publication (Box 40, Folder 41)
    Author: J. Kuczynski & M. Heinemann
- Box: 40, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Contrato Laboral, 1965; Publication (Box 40, Folder 42)
    Author: Angel Castro
- Box: 40, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Creation of Workers in the Post-Gandhian Period, Publication (Box 40, Folder 43)
    Author: U.N. Dhebar
- Box: 40, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Labor in Indonesia, 1963; Publication (Box 40, Folder 44)
- Box: 40, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Changing Patterns of Japanese Life, 1970; Publication (Box 40, Folder 45)
    Author: Robert E. Cole
  - Item 2: Changing Pattern of Japanese Attitudes Toward Work: A Consequence of Recent High Economic Growth, 1969; Publication (Box 40, Folder 45)
    Author: Hiroshi Komai
  - Item 3: Wages and Labor Situation in Today's Japan, 1965; Publication (Box 40, Folder 45)
    Author: Japan Federation of Employers' Associations
- Box: 40, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: The Labor Situation in Korea, 1968; Publication (Box 40, Folder 46)
    Author: American Embassy
- Box: 40, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Survey of the Alliance for Progress, 1968; Publication (Box 40, Folder 47)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Foreign Relations
    Notes: July 15, 1968
  - Item 2: The Labor Elite in Lain America: Is It Revolutionary?, 1966; Publication (Box 40, Folder 47)
    Author: Henry A. Landsberger
- Box: 41, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Joint Industry Promotion Funds and Joint Labor-Management Boards, 1969; Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Notes: October 6, 1969
- Box: 41, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Labor in Mexico, 1963; Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Box: 41, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Life and Labour in Natal, 1952; Publication (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Box: 41, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Verslag Over de Werkzaamheden Van de Stitting Van Den Arbeid, 1946; Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
    Author: Stichting Van Den Arbeid
    Notes: May 1945-1946
- Box: 41, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Economic Changes in Each New Hampshire County, 1965; Publication (Box 41, Folder 5)